According to today's changing lifestyle,
health
insurance has become a very important thing for anyone.
Considering the way medical treatment expenses are increasing,
health insurance is very
important for the future. Now, the first thing that comes to our mind is
which insurance company's plan will be
best for us and our family.
For this, we have brought a
list of toxic health insurance plans, which we will
discuss further. The first plan is Aditya
Birla Activate Shop Diamond Line,
provided by Tilak. Activate and Diamond
Plan are considered the base plans in the insurance market.
This plan provides
health insurance cover ranging from Rs 2 lakh to Rs 2 crore.
Some of its features are as follows: In-
patient hospitalization, where a person is
hospitalized for more than 24 hours, the expenses of
room rent, doctor consultations,
operation theatre, medicine, drugs etc. are covered.
Here, the hospital
question line is available, where the
insurance policy covers the expenses of 30 days before hospitalization.
Post-hospitalization is directly covered
where the insurance policy covers the expenses of 30 days before hospitalization.  This policy covers expenses incurred for seven days even after discharge from the hospital.
This policy
covers basic life care procedure treatment.
In this, the person gets a sum insured
ring statement, where even if the person
uses the entire sum assured, the
insurance company should reimburse it from its side.
Here the person gets things like
road ambulance cover, hospital expenses,
Ayurvedic, homeopathic
treatment cover, Delhi allowance, health
facility, secondary opinion, room upgrade,
domiciliary hospitalization and tax
benefits. The second plan
which we will talk about is the Universal Plan with
Essential Prabal Expense. Here a person can get
health cover ranging from Rs 6 lakh to Rs 10 lakh.
This plan comes with an increase in life
and it covers the cost of procedures by paying Rs 141.
Due to domiciliary hospitalization, the person can also get treatment at home.
In this plan also, the person
gets 30 days of hospitalization and
post graduation of the patients. Among other features,
here the person gets inpatient
hospitalization or  Donor facility,
ambulance and child coverage, vaccination, hospitalization cover,
Delhi cash, critical illness coverage,
sub-limited donors' grace period, tax
benefits.
Medical screening is compulsory for this plan. The
third plan is Religare's Care Health
Insurance Plan. Compared to other plans,
this plan
offers a no-claim bonus. If a person
fails to report his/her death during his/her polytechnic and postgraduate studies, the company increases his/her insurance cover
by 50% the following year. Here, a
person can avail health cover ranging from Rs 4 lakh to Rs 6 crore.
Like the bike insurance plan, the
Religare Care Health Insurance Plan
also offers hospitalization cover, post office
collection cover,
statement, Ayurvedic, homeopathic
treatment cover, second opinion option,
ambulance cover, Delhi Cantt and City coverage, and tax
benefits. The fourth plan is Star
Health's Family Health Optima Plan. In this
plan, a person can
avail health cover ranging from Rs 3 lakh to Rs 25 lakh. Along with the increase in life,
all these benefits are available from here, including
room rent facility and no-expenses sub-limits.
Air Ambulance Cover Ambulance Cover
Newborn Baby Shower Bonus Alternative
Treatments and Medical Opinion The fifth
plan is Max Bupa's Help Companies
plan. Here, a person can avail insurance ranging from Rs 3 lakh to Rs 1
crore.
With lifetime validity, in this plan, the person
gets all the benefits: Domiciliary
Hospitalization Emergency Ambulance Hannibal
White Vaccination Reply for Mixed In-
Patient Care Priyanka Ko Sterilization IS
Due Course Coverage Living Organ Donor
Transplant Waste
Coat 56 is fair co
Optima Restore plan by Health Insurance Here, a
person can avail insurance ranging from Rs 3 lakh to Rs 50 lakh
with life immunity.
In this plan, the person gets all the benefits:
Cardiac Procedures Pain Post
Graduation Organ Donor Cover Ambulance Cover
Your Opinion Delhi Cash for Writing Shadow
Combination Domiciliary Treatment In-Patient
Hospitalization Critical Advantage Rider
Discounts Pre-existing Diseases
Waiting Period More information related to health insurance plan
Visit policy.com today for more information.
Your Trusted Insurance
Advisor
[Music]
Luti